Guide to the Linda Mary Montano Papers MSS.386
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Non-commercially Released Media
  - Subseries B: Video recordings
    - "Chakraphonics: PAL", 1996; ID: 386.0228 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0228)
      "TRT 32:00. stereo"
    - "Chakraphonics: Revised", May 12, 1997; ID: 386.0229 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0229)
    - "Chakraphonics: Revised", May 12, 1997; ID: 386.0230 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0230)
    - "Chakraphonics: Revised", May 12, 1997; ID: 386.0231 (Box 61, Media ID: 386.0231)
    - "Chakraphonics with Jackie Gleason", April 27, 1998; ID: 386.0232 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0232)
      "45 minutes."
    - "Chakraphonics with Jackie Gleason", April 27, 1998; ID: 386.0233 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0233)
    - "Chakraphonics with Jackie Gleason", April 27, 1998; ID: 386.0234 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0234)
    - "Chakraphonics with Jackie Gleason", April 27, 1998; ID: 386.0235 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0235)
      "45 minutes"
    - "Chakraphonics with Jackie Gleason", 1998; ID: 386.0236 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0236)
      "46:12, Video Data Bank"
    - "The Chicken Who Learned How To Fly", 1985; ID: 386.0237 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0237)
      "12 mins. Story: Linda Montano. Music: Pauline Oliveros. Engineer: Brooks Williams. Narrator: Ingrid. Chicken: Mollie. Swan: Tara. Duck: Toby."
    - "Chicken Woman, 1972" Linda Montano, ID: 386.0238 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0238)
      "segment edit for MADE IN CALIFORNIA"
    - "Chini + Papa + Children", undated; ID: 386.0239 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0239)
      "12 min"
      Original format: miniDV.
    - "Chini - From Movie", undated; ID: 386.0240 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0240)
      "Super 8 Dub"
    - "Cinderella" Linda Montano, undated; ID: 386.0241 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0241)
    - "Coca", April 27, 1990; ID: 386.0242 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0242)
    - "Dad Art", April 19, 2005; ID: 386.0243 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0243)
      Originally under the label "Dad Art."
    - "Dad Art", 2005; ID: 386.0244 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0244)
      Originally under Montano's label "Dad Art."
      "1 Hr 55 Minutes; Linda M. Montano"
    - "Dad Art", 2005; ID: 386.0245 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0245)
    - "Dad Art", undated; ID: 386.0246 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0246)
      "2 hrs, 30 min. Linda M."
    - "Dad Art Performance Tape", 2005; ID: 386.0247 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0247)
    - "Dad Art Performance: with Time Code", 2010; ID: 386.0248 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0248)
    - "Dad Art Rough: Time Code", April 22, 2005; ID: 386.0249 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0249)
    - "Dad Art Rough: Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0250 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0250)
      "1 hr, 55 min"
    - "Dad Art: Tape 7", December 26, 2004; ID: 386.0251 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0251)
      "Tape 7; Last Before 2nd Stroke; Happy Birthday"
    - "Dad Art: Time Code", March 30, 2005; ID: 386.0252 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0252)
      "2nd correction"
    - "Dad: Canada", undated; ID: 386.0253 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0253)
      "Eat/Outside; Tape 6"
    - "Dad Document", undated; ID: 386.0254 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0254)
      "7 Sacraments/Beatitudes; 30 min.!"
    - "Dad Paint", undated; ID: 386.0255 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0255)
      "Best of Dad Painting - Not in Video"
    - "Dad Part I, Tape 1", 2001-2002; ID: 386.0256 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0256)
    - "Dad Raw Footage Part II, Tape 2", 2001-2002; ID: 386.0257 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0257)
    - "Dad Raw #3", undated; ID: 386.0258 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0258)
      "B-day Cake; start here for end; + caretaker"
    - "The Day After the Night Before", February 5, 1988; ID: 386.0259 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0259)
      "Starring Myriam Abramowicz, documented by Helene Aylon. Sherry."
    - "Devi Mahatmyam: Ch. 12, 13", March 26, 1988; ID: 386.0260 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0260)
      "Betsy Ceva, Nadananda"
    - "Dr. Jane Gooding", undated; ID: 386.0261 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0261)
      Originally under Montano's label "Learning to Talk."
      "Do not rewind. Dr. Jane Gooding T1+2 Original."
    - "Dr. Jane Gooding", undated; ID: 386.0262 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0262)
      "Start at 90"
    - "Doctor Nurse", undated; ID: 386.0263 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0263)
    - "Dystonia", October 8, 2009; ID: 386.0264 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0264)
      "19 minutes"
    - "Dystonia", October 6, 2009; ID: 386.0265 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0265)
    - "El Chow de Faustine", October 1994; ID: 386.0266 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0266)
      "Open Studio w/ Linda Montano. 'Lenny Golden'"
    - "Elders", undated; ID: 386.0267 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0267)
      "Flo Monroe, Holley, Dr. Johnson, Cindy"
    - "Elders Tape 1", undated; ID: 386.0268 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0268)
      "Elders Tape 1: Tony, Celia, Mom, Dr. Ash, Vera"
    - "Elders Tape 2", undated; ID: 386.0269 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0269)
      "1 hr."
    - "Elders Tape 3", undated; ID: 386.0270 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0270)
      "48 minutes. Dr. Johnson, Andy, Seamus, Luba"
    - "Elders Tape 1: With Time Code", 2003; ID: 386.0271 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0271)
      "Tony, Cecelia, Mom, Dr. Ash, Vera"
    - "Elders Tape 2: With Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0272 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0272)
      "Irma, Dr. Hull, Agnes, Flo, Holly"
    - "Elders Tape 3: With Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0273 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0273)
      "Dr. Johnson, Andy, Lights, Luba"
    - "The End Is Near: Edit", undated; ID: 386.0274 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0274)
      "21:19; color."
    - "Enter - A Fairy Tale: Time Code", July 10, 2011; ID: 386.0275 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0275)
    - "Facial Expressions for Chakra", undated; ID: 386.0276 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0276)
      "Netti (Nasal) / Accupuncture / Eyes"
    - "Family + Old People + Sister Rose", undated; ID: 386.0277 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0277)
    - "Father LeBar", December 10, 2009; ID: 386.0278 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0278)
      "Next to Last"
    - "Father Lebar: Test", October 7, 2008; ID: 386.0279 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0279)
      "No Time Code"
    - "Father Lebar: Time Code", November 7, 2006; ID: 386.0280 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0280)
      Originally under Montano's label "Father Lebar."
    - "A Few Visuals", undated; ID: 386.0281 (Box 62, Media ID: 386.0281)
    - "Five Minute Greeting: Reunion", undated; ID: 386.0282 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0282)
    - "Flower", undated; ID: 386.0283 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0283)
      Originally under Montano's label "Manda Barbour; 7 Spiritual Lives of LM"
    - "Flowers", undated; ID: 386.0284 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0284)
    - "Flowers", undated; ID: 386.0285 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0285)
      "49.50 min"
    - "Flowers: Linda and Steven", undated; ID: 386.0286 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0286)
    - "For Elaine, Love Linda as Hilary Clinton", 2004; ID: 386.0287 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0287)
    - "For Elaine Summers: a Tribute", August 2004; ID: 386.0288 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0288)
      "Love from: Linda M. Montano; 7 min. tape"
    - "For Linda from Sherlah", undated; ID: 386.0289 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0289)
      Originally under Montano's label "Student and Fan Work."
    - "Forgiveness Room", undated; ID: 386.0290 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0290)
      "1 hour"
    - "The Forgiveness Room" Linda Montano, undated; ID: 386.0291 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0291)
    - "The Forgiveness Room" Linda Montano, undated; ID: 386.0292 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0292)
    - "French Woman Leading Lullaby: Sonic Meditation", undated; ID: 386.0293 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0293)
    - "Ganna Montano Talks About His Sister Linda + Father Henry", 2004; ID: 386.0294 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0294)
    - "Ha! Ha! 'Is That All There Is?'", 2007; ID: 386.0295 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0295)
      "10 Minutes. A Film by Linda M. Montano."
    - "Handcuff", October 1997; ID: 386.0296 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0296)
      "Peter Kirby, Media Art Services. Remaster of 1/2" open reel to 3/4" SP. Audio: mixed. trt: 20:08. Tech: JS"
    - "Handcuff with Tom Marioni" Linda Montano, undated; ID: 386.0297 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0297)
      "20:08; 'Dear Linda - Returning this. Unfortunately, the quality is not good enough to use in show. -Connie'"
    - "Henry Montano Eating and Painting", September 2004; ID: 386.0298 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0298)
      "Linda Montano, Please Return; Tape 5; Sept. 04"
    - "I Value Your Opinion" Sara Pomerance, 2006; ID: 386.0229 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0229)
      "4 min."
    - "Icky and Kathy Trilogy" Kathy High, 1999; ID: 386.0300 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0300)
      "9 minutes"
    - "Irma Sagazie Testimonial", 2003; ID: 386.0301 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0301)
    - "Irma Sagazie Testimonial", undated; ID: 386.0302 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0302)
    - "Karate Exam", December 1982; ID: 386.0303 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0303)
    - "Karate Exam" Linda Montano, December 1982; ID: 386.0304 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0304)
    - "Kathy High Dad", undated; ID: 386.0305 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0305)
    - "Learning to Talk", 1976-1977; ID: 386.0306 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0306)
      "Center for Music Experiment"
    - "Learning to Talk", undated; ID: 386.0307 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0307)
      "Dub: Curve Phillips"
    - "Learning to Talk", undated; ID: 386.0308 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0308)
      "A video, characters that I have developed to get over fear of talking."
    - "Learning to Talk: B + W Original", 1977; ID: 386.0309 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0309)
    - "Learning to Talk: For Master", undated; ID: 386.0310 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0310)
    - "Learning to Talk, Rope Piece Film Document, Mitchell's Death", undated; ID: 386.0311 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0311)
    - "Leftovers", undated; ID: 386.0312 (Box 63, Media ID: 386.0312)
      Originally under Montano's label "Sex."
    - "Letters from Linda M. Montano", 2005; ID: 386.0313 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0313)
      "The National Review of Live Art"
    - "Lighten Up: Time Code", 2010; ID: 386.0314 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0314)
    - "Linda + Tehching Boxing", 1983; ID: 386.0315 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0315)
    - "Linda as Hilary Clinton with Martha Wilson", June 2000; ID: 386.0316 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0316)
    - "Linda Chants Chini + Papa with Children", undated; ID: 386.0317 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0317)
    - "Linda/Les and Annie", undated; ID: 386.0318 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0318)
    - "Linda M. Montano for Window at New Museum", 1995; ID: 386.0319 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0319)
    - "Linda Montano", undated; ID: 386.0320 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0320)
    - "Linda Montano 1 Dad", undated; ID: 386.0321 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0321)
      "Working Tape 1-5"
    - "Linda Montano 2 Father", undated; ID: 386.0322 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0322)
    - "Linda Montano 3 Father", undated; ID: 386.0323 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0323)
    - "Linda Montano 4 Father", undated; ID: 386.0324 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0324)
    - "Linda Montano 5 Father", undated; ID: 386.0325 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0325)
    - "Linda Montano 6 Father", undated; ID: 386.0326 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0326)
    - "Linda Montano 7 Father", undated; ID: 386.0327 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0327)
    - "Linda Montano 9 Father", undated; ID: 386.0328 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0328)
    - "Linda Montano at the New Museum", December 6, 1991; ID: 386.0329 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0329)
      "Tape 1 of 1. Copy"
    - "Linda Montano Father 1: Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0330 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0330)
    - "Linda Montano Father 2: Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0331 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0331)
    - "Linda Montano Father 3: Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0332 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0332)
    - "Linda Montano Father 4: Time Code", undated; ID: 386.0333 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0333)
    - "Linda Montano Father 5", undated; ID: 386.0334 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0334)
    - "Linda Montano Father 6", undated; ID: 386.0335 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0335)
      "Maybe last one; Cake B-Day Last"
    - "Linda Montano Father 7", undated; ID: 386.0336 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0336)
    - "Linda Montano Father 8: Empty", undated; ID: 386.0337 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0337)
    - "Linda Montano Father 9", undated; ID: 386.0338 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0338)
      "Paint, Eat, TV, Bed, Diaper, Water Massage Feet/Hands, Linda Walk; Day before stroke; 50:35"
    - "The Linda Montano 'Have You Had a Religious Experience?' Hour", undated; ID: 386.0339 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0339)
    - "Linda Montano: Indiana State University (copy)", September 30, 1993; ID: 386.0390 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0390)
    - "Linda Montano Message to the Public", March 1990; ID: 386.0341 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0341)
    - "Linda Montano: Palm Reading, Performance Teaching, Telephone Tarot, Art/Life Counseling", undated; ID: 386.0342 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0342)
      "Linda Montano Proposal Description: Tape Sample. In 1976 I made a tape, LEARNING TO TALK. Seven parts of me told success stories, one from each chakra. In 1984 I began 7 YEARS OF LIVING ART and lived each chakra, one a year. In this tape I describe this progression from making a tape (1976), to making myself (1984-91), to making a tape to teach others how to make themselves."
    - "Linda Montano Performance Background", undated; ID: 386.0343 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0343)
      "Please Note: Thirty Seconds of White Leader: Begin Five Seconds In On First Color (Red). For Linda Montano."
    - "Linda Montano's Family", undated; ID: 386.0344 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0344)
      "45 min."
    - "Linda Montano's St. Teresa of Avila", undated; ID: 386.0345 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0345)
      "39 minutes"
    - "Love Sex", May 21, 1997; ID: 386.0346 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0346)
      "80:00"
    - "Love Sex", May 21, 1997; ID: 386.0347 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0347)
      "Love Sex - Images on this tape - 1. Nasal with heart over clouds, red around edge - 2. Clouds nice - 3. Put honey in eyes - 4. Clouds - 5. Better eyes "crying" - 6. Sky - 7. Lick fingers - 8. Accupuncture - 9. Sky - 10. Eyes - 11. Dancing birds."
    - "Love Sex" Linda Montano, May 21, 1997; ID: 386.0348 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0348)
    - "Luba/Forgiveness for Mexico Coop Master", undated; ID: 386.0349 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0349)
    - "Masks", 2009; ID: 386.0350 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0350)
      "Glitch 20:40. 1 Hour 4 Minutes."
    - "Matagi: Interview", undated; ID: 386.0351 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0351)
    - "Matagi Super 8 Movie", undated; ID: 386.0352 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0352)
      "Walk and Pick Vegetables"
    - "Mehta Document(ary)", undated; ID: 386.0353 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0353)
      Originally under Montano's label "Two Ayruvedic Doctors."
      "Super VHS"
    - "Mehta Documentary", undated; ID: 386.0354 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0354)
    - "Mehta Documentary", undated; ID: 386.0355 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0355)
    - "Mehta Documentary: Dub", undated; ID: 386.0356 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0356)
    - "Mehtas + Tai Chi", undated; ID: 386.0357 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0357)
    - "MetamorphoSex" Rose Hansen, undated; ID: 386.0358 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0358)
    - "Miracle of Birth", undated; ID: 386.0359 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0359)
    - "Mitchell Payne Slides: Master", undated; ID: 386.0360 (Box 64, Media ID: 386.0360)
      Originally under Montano's label "Mitchell's Death."
      "Mitchell Payne: photos of Mitchell. Photos of photos. Original."
    - "Mitchell's Death", October 1997; ID: 386.0361 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0361)
      "Peter Kirby, Media Art Services. Remaster of 1/2" open reel to 3/4" SP. Audio: mixed. trt: 22:45. Tech: JS"
    - "Mitchell's Death", undated; ID: 386.0302 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0302)
      "21 minutes. 2 dubs."
    - "Mitchell's Death", undated; ID: 386.0363 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0363)
      "21 minutes. Tape starts at 40 seconds. Ends at 23 minutes, 0 seconds."
    - "Mitchell's Death", undated; ID: 386.0364 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0364)
      "Begin at the Beginning"
    - "Mitchell's Death: A Film by Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0365 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0365, Case 386.0365)
      "23 minutes"
      Access DVD is available for reading room viewing only.
    - "Mitchell's Death: Art/Life One Year Performance, Fleming Museum", undated; ID: 386.0366 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0366)
      "21 minutes."
    - "Mitchell's Death: Original", 1977; ID: 386.0367 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0367)
    - "Mitchell's Death: Original", undated; ID: 386.0368 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0368)
      Original format: U-matic SP.
    - "Mitchell's Death; Putting on Make Up", 1978; ID: 386.0369 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0369)
      "Do not use sound. Only image. Put on needles for performance original. U.C.S.D 1978."
    - "Mitchell's Death w/Echo", undated; ID: 386.0370 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0370)
    - "Mom Art: Time Code", November 1, 2011; ID: 386.0371 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0371)
    - "Mom Art: Time Code Test", March 7, 2012; ID: 386.0372 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0372)
    - "Monster Fighter" Leslie Crawford, undated; ID: 386.0373 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0373)
    - "Montano as Mother Teresa: Time Code", July 8, 2009; ID: 386.0374 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0374)
    - "Montano: Segal '97", 1997; ID: 386.0375 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0375)
      "Hyde Park"
    - "Montano Slides", undated; ID: 386.0376 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0376)
    - "Mother: Fairy Tale", undated; ID: 386.0377 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0377)
    - "Mother Teresa plus Fairy Tale", 2010; ID: 386.0378 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0378)
      "Version 3"
    - "Movie About Flowers", undated; ID: 386.0379 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0379)
      "Scientific; 24 min."
    - "My Little Pony in E.P.", undated; ID: 386.0380 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0380)
      "44 min."
    - "My Pope Dream", August 14, 2013; ID: 386.0381 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0381)
      "14:08 min."
    - "Nadia Grozlovow", undated; ID: 386.0382 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0382)
      "500 Hoola"
    - "Nurse! Nurse!: No Time Code", March 26, 2013; ID: 386.0383 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0383)
    - "Oak Harbor", undated; ID: 386.0384 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0384)
    - "Oh Say Can You See: Dub", 1978; ID: 386.0385 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0385)
      "Linda Montano (1978) Dub. 'Stay Tuned' Exhibition, New Museum 7/81"
    - "On Death and Dying" Linda Montano, 1982; ID: 386.0386 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0386)
      "22 min. The Art Institute of Chicago"
    - "On Death and Dying: Master Edit", November 1982; ID: 386.0387 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0387)
      "Recorded live on Ch. 6 Woodstock. Color. 22 minutes."
    - "Passion of Joan of Arc", undated; ID: 386.0388 (Box 65, Media ID: 386.0388)
    - "Pauline Oliveros", May 9, 1979; cuid41207 (Box 65, U-matic ID: 386.0389)
      "Music Track only. Dub I color. 'I met Pauline Oliveros in March, 1975 and have documented the relationship in many ways for these 5 years. It fascinates me to think that we were all infants, or 11 years old or rode horses at amusement parks as children. When I found old photographs of Pauline I was able to visually observe the history of her life. Yes, even Pauline Oliveros was once five....' -Linda Montano."
    - "Pauline Oliveros: Music and Voice", undated; ID: 386.0390 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0390)
      "Original; color."
    - "Pe.A.Ch.: 337C: Topics May Vary: A Tribute to Linda Montano", October 9, 1997; ID: 386.0391 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0391)
      "[PErformance Art CHurch] Hosts: Olivia Aldin, S. Alton Dulaney, Tiana Hux. Music: Graham Reynolds and Kim Hill"
    - "People at CME", May 25, 1978; ID: 386.0392 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0392)
      "Marsha, Debbie, Phil, Rob, Linda, Terri, Albert, Ed, Jean Charles, Pauline, David, Roger, Richard, Joan, Bruce R., Glyn, Bruce L., Linda."
    - "Performance Class: Soap Operas", undated; ID: 386.0393 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0393)
      "Chicago"
    - "Pool Performance", February 19, 1988; ID: 386.0394 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0394)
      "Camera: Michael A. Lucas. OSU '88."
    - "Pre-Thesis Performance #4" Manda Barbour, undated; ID: 386.0395 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0395)
    - "Pre-Thesis Performance #5" Manda Barbour, undated; ID: 386.0396 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0396)
    - "Primal Scenes", 2004; ID: 386.0397 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0397)
      "10 min."
    - "Primal Scenes: Dub II", March 17, 1980; ID: 386.0398 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0398)
    - "R Bjerum - Original", undated; ID: 386.0399 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0399)
      "Cancer/Bed/Money; Jaiiv Song with Ganesh/Shiva Parvatii; L. Montano '95"
    - "Raw Footage of Girls Dancing and Waving", 1998; ID: 386.0400 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0400)
    - "Rejuvenation + AIDS" Dr. Mehta, April 1991; ID: 386.0401 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0401)
    - "Relationships", December 1982; ID: 386.0402 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0402)
      "Color; 14 minutes. Heart w/VIcky [Sterup], [Ellen] Cross, Montano as Heart Specialist."
    - "Response to Linda Weintraub's Oberlin Artists" Linda Montano, October 31, 2000; ID: 386.0403 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0403)
      "Halloween Day"
    - "Rites of Passion", undated; ID: 386.0404 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0404)
    - "Rope Piece: High Performance", undated; ID: 386.0405 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0405)
      "Linda Montano and Tehching Hsieh: Master; approx. 16 mins."
    - "Rose Song", undated; ID: 386.0406 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0406)
      "Rose Song with Oliveros; 10 min."
    - "Sachicoism 3", September 1981; ID: 386.0407 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0407)
      Originally under Montano's label "Sachicoism: Kioki, Japan"
      "28 minutes. Directed by Keisuke Oki 2-27-9. Megurohoncho, Meguro-ku, Tokyo/52. Japan"
    - "Sacred Sex", undated; ID: 386.0408 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0408)
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: Complete", undated; ID: 386.0409 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0409)
      Originally under Montano's label "Teresa of Avila."
      "Linda Montano; 3"
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: Footage not used for T of Avila", undated; ID: 386.0410 (Box 66, Media ID: 386.0410)
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: Revised", June 25, 2007; ID: 386.0411 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0411)
      "By Linda Mary Montano; 38 minutes"
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: 2nd to Last Edit", undated; ID: 386.0412 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0412)
      "2nd to Last Edit not 2 bad; a John St."
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: Time Code", March 29, 2007; ID: 386.0413 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0413)
      "37 minutes"
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: Work Tape 1", undated; ID: 386.0414 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0414)
    - "St. Teresa of Avila: Work Tape 2", undated; ID: 386.0415 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0415)
    - "St. Teresa Working Tape", undated; ID: 386.0416 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0416)
      "36 min."
    - "St. Teresa Working Tape 1", undated; ID: 386.0417 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0417)
      "Rosary beads, Communion, baby, tube in nose"
    - "St. Teresa Working Tape 2", undated; ID: 386.0418 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0418)
      "Nun, Nose, Kids Wave. 8 min."
    - "St. Teresa Working Tape 3", undated; ID: 386.0419 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0419)
      "Accupuncture, Sky. 40 min."
    - "Seven Chakras: Time Code Test", August 12, 2011; ID: 386.0420 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0420)
    - "The Seven Lives of Linda Montano: Original Source Footage", undated; ID: 386.0421 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0421)
    - "The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", April 12, 1996; ID: 386.0422 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0422)
      "TRT: 12:49"
    - "Seven Stages of Intoxication", April 26, 1995; ID: 386.0478 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0478)
      Duration: 34 min.
    - "Seven Stages of Intoxication: Edited Master", April 26, 1995; ID: 386.0423 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0423)
      "Stereo; TRT: 34:00"
    - "Seven Stages of Intoxication: Original Raw Footage Unedited", undated; ID: 386.0424 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0424)
    - "Seven Years: 1st Cut", undated; ID: 386.0425 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0425)
      "Maida Barbour"
    - "Seven Years of Living Art", undated; ID: 386.0426 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0426)
      "Producer: Maida Barbour; Running Time: 13:03"
    - "Seven Years of Living Art", undated; ID: 386.0427 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0427)
      "Producer: Maida Barbour. Running Time: 13:03"